So I want to edit the prompts that I already added.
It was, I want to create an image out of a building.
Yes, so I completed out of a building which is the,
which is going to be the head quarters of my educational company.
I've provided you with its logo, name, colors, and phones,
summaries, let's say the logo, right?
The logo and the name, I provided you with its logo.
So let's say I want to create an image out of a building,
my educational company called the take of college.
I've provided you with its logo and I want you to also add up a big flag
of the logo, like near the building or something like that.
And I want the entire image to be the most realistic possible that it feels.
It doesn't even feel fake in no ways, right?
So this is what we got.